翻譯：SystemNT-ch@subhd.com
（轉載，壓制請保留譯者信息）
早上好 夥計們 過得怎麼樣？
Man: Good morning, guys. How's it going?
貝利  還好嗎？
Bailey, what's up?
你還好嗎？
What's up?
嘿 休伊 嘿 沃森 過得怎麼樣？
Hey, chewy. Hey, Watson, how's it going?
看起來不錯
Looking good.
奎妮  調皮鬼
Queenie, rascal.
好的 想要些吃的嗎？要些吃的嗎？
Okay. Want some food, want some food?
大口吃吧
Wolf it down.
夠了  這就是你今天所有的食物
That's it, that's all you get.
要喝水嗎？
Water?
你好嗎？
- - How are you?
她在這裏  她在這裏
There she is, there she is.
好的 好 萊克西 好的
Okay, all right, Lexi, all right.
嘿
Hey.
退後點 退後點
Back it up, back it up.
嘿  萊克西 退後點
Hey, Lexi. Back it up.
嘿 嘿 嘿 大狗狗
Hey, hey. Hey, big doggie.
大狗狗  大狗狗
Big doggie, big doggie.
霍莉對嗎？
Holly, right?
霍莉·加寧
Holly garling.
嗨  你還好嗎？
Hi. How are you?
嗨  抱歉  咱們認識嗎？
Hi. I'm sorry, do we know each other?
噢  我叫賽斯 以前是西布魯克高中的
Oh, Seth. West brook high.
- 噢  咱們同班嗎？- 我比你大一屆
- Oh. Were you in my class? - Oh, I was in the year above you.
我們雖然沒有一起玩過或是什麼的
We didn't hang out or anything,
但我知道你是誰
but I knew who you were.
真的嗎？
You did?
當然 每個人都認識你
Sure, everybody did.
我不知道這事兒
I don't know about that.
所以你現在成為一名作家了嗎？
So you're a writer now, huh?
那很酷  很好
That's cool. That's great.
是啊 這身女服務員裝扮
Yeah. This whole waitressing uniform,
其實是一個偽裝
it's just a disguise.
但確實很像
It's convincing.
我剛都想管你要一份冰淇淋聖代
I was gonna order an ice cream sundae.
- 另加點巧克力末 - 你不會是第一個這麼想的
- Extra sprinkles. - You wouldn't be the first.
- 我到站了 - 哦 你要在這兒..？
- This is my stop. - Oh, this is you?
很高興見到你
It was nice to see you again.
也很高興見到你 嘿 如果沒什麼事的話..
Nice to see you too. Hey, if you're not doing anything...
...一起喝一杯咖啡
...get a coffee.
資料：霍莉·加寧 居住在洛杉磯 單身
內特..
他在這兒  那個男人在這兒
There he is. There's the man.
- 內特 問你個問題 - 嗯？
- Nate, let me ask you a question. - Hmm?
如果有這麼個女孩  你想讓她注意到你...
If there was this girl and you wanted her to notice you...
你現在是認真的嗎？
Are you serious right now?
是啊
Yeah.
去 哥們 我和你不熟
Shit, man, i don't know you.
我不知道你在玩什麼把戲 為什麼要來問我？
I don't know what kind of game you got. What are you asking me?
抱歉  我想也許...
Sorry. I thought maybe...
聽著 等等...你喜歡一個女孩對嗎？
Listen, wait... You like this girl?
- 我們現在聊的是女孩嗎？- 是的 女孩
-  We are talking about a girl here right? - Yes, girl.
我真的喜歡她
I do like her.
那就自信點  知道嗎？
So just confident, you know?
做個自信的男人  懂得如何逗樂她們
Guy who's confident. Knows how to make them laugh.
和她們聊你的日常  裝作很牛的樣子
Tell 'em about your day. Act like you give a shit.
我意思是  這並沒有那麼神秘難懂
I mean, it ain't a mystery.
自信 有趣  讓她們笑
Confident, funny, make 'em laugh.
明白了 很好 謝謝
Got it. Good. Thanks.
嘿 別再來問我這種問題懂嗎？
Hey, and no more bringing this shit to me, all right?
你和我  咱們交情還沒到那份兒上
You and me, we ain't like that.
明白
Cool.
賽斯   傑塞普博士需要你的幫助
Seth, Dr. Jessup needs your help.
他要殺了關在34號籠的那只德牧
He's putting down the German Shepherd in 34.
萊克西
Lexi.
聽著 你人挺不錯 但如果你不能做好工作
Look, you're a sweet guy. But if you can't do your job,
我會把你換掉
I'll find someone who can.
- 清楚嗎？- 她是一條很棒的狗
- Is that clear? - She's a really good dog.
嗨  萊克西 嘿
Hey, Lexi. Hey.
事情是這樣的  我們只是...
Here's the thing, we just--
嘿 女孩
hey, girl.
嘿 萊克西 嘿
Hey, Lexi. Hey.
怎麼樣？想出去走走嗎？
How's it going? Wanna go for a walk?
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
好女孩 很激動對嗎？
Good girl. Yeah, it's exciting, isn't it?
好吧 萊克西 咱們開始
All right, Lexi. Here we go.
好 這是條好狗
All right, that's a good dog.
這是條好狗
Yeah, that's a good dog.
- 你沒事吧？- 她真是一個好狗
- Dr. Jessup: You all right? - Yeah, she's just a good dog.
噓 沒關係的  萊克西 沒事的
Shh, it's okay, Lexi. It's all right.
想要她的話 你可以永遠留著她
You want her, you can always keep her.
我住的那樓不允許養寵物
My building doesn't allow pets.
非常嚴格
Very strict.
那就找個新家唄
Fucking find a new place.
我工作一小時才賺9美元啊？有自來水就不錯了
$9.00 an hour? I'm lucky I have running water.
這就是你的問題所在 你沒有主動權
That's your whole problem. You got no initiative.
這也是你一把年紀了還在做這種低級工作的原因
It's how come you're still working in a shit hole like this at your age.
一生中你想要什麼
You want something in this life,
你就得去爭取它
you gotta take it.
所以現在怎麼樣？
So what's it gonna be?
我意思是 你想要她的話 就給你留著
I mean, you want her, she's yours.
動手吧 快
Do it, do it already.
好的  萊克西  開始了
All right, Lexi. Here we go.
你是條好狗
You're a good dog.
穩住  你是條好狗
Hold still. You're a good dog.
嗨 霍莉 嘿
Seth: Hey, Holly, hey.
你幾點吃午飯的？
What time do you get lunch?
你什麼時候吃午飯？
我一點鐘吃午飯
I get lunch at 1:00.
一點鐘
1:00.
嘿 嘿 嗨
Hey, hey, hi.
嘿...嘿 記得我嗎？
Hey... Hey, remember me?
沒錯
That's right.
呃 我想要張單人桌
Uh, well, i guess table for one while I'm here,
但我在想
but really I was just wondering
遲些時候能請你吃晚餐嗎
if you wanted to get maybe dinner later.
不知道你怎麼樣  但我挺喜歡海鮮的
I don't know about you, but I love seafood.
噢 真的嗎？是的 我就點這些了
Oh, you do? Yeah, that's all I eat.
海鮮 海鮮...
Seafood, seafood...
有一個 呃...有一個地方
There's a, uh-- there's a place on--
那有一個地方
there's a place on--
在威爾希爾有一個肉蟹大排檔
there's a place on Wilshire called the crab joint.
哦 你知道？是 我們可以...今晚？
Oh, you know it? Yeah, we could-- tonight?
它..嘿 霍莉 嘿
It's-- hey, Holly, hey.
嘿 霍莉 還好嗎？
Hey, Holly. How's it going?
嘿...
Hey...
- 嗨  還有位置嗎？ - 您坐哪都行
- Hi. Anywhere? - Yeah, anywhere is fine.
好的 謝謝
Okay. Thanks.
嘿 你好 我是霍莉
Hey, how are you? I'm Holly.
今天我為您服務
I'll be taking care of you today.
你肯定是一個作家
You must be a writer.
- 什麼？-  一名作家
- I'm sorry? - Seth: A writer.
在公共汽車上偽裝的那個
The disguise from the bus.
我們幾天前在公交車上見過面
We met a couple of days ago on the bus.
- 我叫賽斯 - 我很抱歉
- My name's Seth. - I'm so sorry.
我記性很差
My memory, it like totally sucks.
您喜歡聽到服務員這麼說對嗎？
I know, just what you want to hear from your waiter, right?
不 沒關係的
No, that's fine.
呃 要不您先點個開胃菜之類的？
Uh, can I get you started with anything? An appetizer?
嗯...
Yeah, um...
那就先來杯水吧
Let's uh-- let's do water.
你回來的時候 我就拿定主意了
And then by the time you come back, I'll know.
水 知道了
Water. Una agua. You got it.
嘿 我喜歡你的頭髮
Hey, um, i like your hair.
和那天公交車上的不一樣
It looks different from the bus.
- 很漂亮 - 謝謝
- It's nice. - Thank you.
你不用感到緊張
Yeah. You shouldn't feel insecure about it
或者不好意思  它..
or self conscious, it's--
是個很美的髮型
is a good haircut.
呃 你先看看菜單
Uh. Why don't you take a look at the menu
我去拿水來
and I will go grab your water.
好的 派
Yeah. Pie.
蘋果派
Apple pie.
您吃的怎麼樣？
How's it going over here?
- 賽斯 - 什麼？
- Seth. - What's that?
賽斯 我的名字叫賽斯
Seth. My name is Seth.
食物怎麼樣 賽斯？
How's the food, Seth?
很美味 很不錯
It's good. It's quality.
實際上 我有個問題想問你
Actually, I had a question for you.
你喜歡Ben folds嗎？
Do you like Ben folds?
我有兩張他本周音樂會的票
'Cause I have a couple of tickets to his concert this week
本來要和我去的那女孩
and the girl i was gonna go with--
不是我女朋友
not a girlfriend or anything--
她有事 沒法去了
she can't make it, she has a thing.
我在想  如果你想去的話...
I was wondering if maybe you'd wanna...
抱歉 我去不了
- Go? - I'm sorry, I can't.
我不喜歡自己一個人去看表演
I don't like going to shows by myself,
那樣感覺有點奇怪 你懂的 所以也許...
it feels kind of strange, you know, so maybe...
這不是什麼大事兒  不需太多顧慮
Not a big deal, no pressure.
咱們只是去看看  不是約會什麼的
We could just go. It wouldn't have to be a date or anything.
關鍵是 我已經有男朋友了 所以...
The thing is, I already sort of have a boyfriend, so...
不 你沒有
No, you don't.
我把賬單擱這兒了
I'm just gonna leave this here.
感謝光臨
Thanks for coming in.
稍等...一下
Hang on a second.
嘿
Hey.
- 外面有個男的 - 哦 性感嗎？
- There's a guy out there. - Ooh, is he hot?
我說真的  克萊爾
I'm serious, Claire.
別疑神疑鬼的 霍莉
Don't get paranoid on me, hol.
疑神疑鬼的時候就沒意思了
You're no fun when you're paranoid.
罷了
Never mind.
賭十塊錢是他掛的
Ten bucks says it's him.
- 喂  埃裏克 - 嘿 寶貝
- Yes, Eric. - Eric: Hey, babe.
- 你想怎樣？ - 天啊 這什麼態度
- Holly: What do you want? - Eric: Jesus, what's with the attitude?
我只想和你說說話  我一直都在想你
I just wanted to talk. I've been thinking about you.
他是不是又喝醉了 多愁善感的？
Is he drunk and weepy again?
一點點
A little bit.
你在和誰說話？和誰在一起是嗎？
Eric: Who are you talking to? You with someone?
別疑神疑鬼的  埃裏克
Don't get paranoid on me, Eric.
疑神疑鬼的時候就沒意思了
You're no fun when you're paranoid.
要再去陪埃裏克一晚嗎？
Claire: So the other night with Eric?
真的嗎？我們還能回到過去嗎？
Really? Are we gonna go there again?
好兩年了 你別跟我說他不重要
He was two years, you can't convince me he never mattered.
我是認真的 霍莉
I'm serious, though, hol.
孤獨可不好受
Being alone is just kinda shitty.
那還能怎樣  要我把他做過的一切都忘了嗎？
So, what, I'm just supposed to forget everything he did?
是的 忘記 原諒 向前看
Yes. Forget, forgive. Move the fuck on already.
回到原來的樣子
Just go back to the way things were.
你知道 我做不到
You know i can't do that.
敬我們
To us.
嘿 薩姆
Hey, Sam.
- 有人很受歡迎喲 - 什麼？
- Someone's popular. - What?
我們把它放在休息室裏了
We put it in the break room.
好的...
Okay...
走運了 婊子 老實交代 他是誰？
Lucky, bitch. Spill. Who's the guy?
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
聽 我很抱歉那天晚上醉酒後給你打電話
Listen, I'm so sorry for the drunk dial the other night.
我意思是 你知道怎麼回事
I mean, you know how it is.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I do.
來瓶啤酒還是其它喝的？
Listen, can I get you a beer or something?
埃裏克 你必須停止做這樣的事情
Eric, you have to stop doing stuff like this.
什麼樣的事情？
Stuff like... What now?
別裝了 那些玫瑰？你知道我最喜歡的
Come on. Roses? You know they're my favorite.
我懵了
I didn't know that.
好吧 算我傻
Okay. Well, now I just feel stupid.
- 就喝一瓶 - 我該走了
- Well-- just one beer. - I should go.
也沒那麼不堪回首對嗎？我們有過一些好時光
It wasn't all bad, right? We had some good times.
是的
Yep.
所以為什麼不再給一次機會呢？
So why don't we give it another shot?
你真的要我說出她的名字嗎？
Are you really gonna make me say her name?
太蠢了
Eric: This is so fucking stupid.
我意思是 咱曾經確實有過不快
I mean, we had something.
曾經
Had.
埃裏克 都是過去的事了
Eric, past tense.
我出去呼吸一下新鮮空氣
I'm gonna get some air.
夜色不錯
Seth: Nice night.
- 是的 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yep.
- 不吸煙嗎？- 我？不吸
- Not a smoker? - Me? No.
那很好
That's good.
永遠別嘗試  這是個壞習慣
Don't ever start, it's a terrible habit.
好的 我不會的
Okay, I won't.
謝謝
Thanks.
- 今宵愉快 - 你喜歡那些花嗎？
- Have a nice night. - You like the flowers?
你看起來像喜歡紅白玫瑰的那種女孩
You seemed like a red and white roses kind of girl.
我只是猜猜而已
It was just a guess.
哦 天哪 你是那天來餐廳的那個男的
Oh, my god. You're that guy from the restaurant.
我叫賽斯
Seth.
你在幹什麼 跟蹤我嗎？
What are you, like, following me or something?
什麼？不是..只是..
What? No. Just...
聽著 我不是變態 明白嗎？
Look, I'm not some psycho, okay?
你知道我 我們在同一所學校上過學
You know me. We went to school together.
你想幹什麼？
What do you want?
我什麼也不要  只想和你聊聊天
I don't want anything. I just want to talk to you.
當我那天在公交車上看到你的時候
When I saw you on the bus the other day,
經過這麼多年後  我對你產生了感覺
after all these years, i felt something.
我知道你也有
I know you did.
我無法擺脫那種感覺
I can't just walk away from that.
- 我根本不瞭解你 - 但你會瞭解
- I don't even know you. - But you will.
- 你可以走 我只是...我能和你聊聊嗎？- 不行
- You can go, I just-- can I just talk to you? - No.
- 嘿 等等 - 不要  不要碰我
- Hey, hang on. - Don't! Don't touch me.
滾開！你在跟我開玩笑嗎？
Move! Are you kidding me?
我只想和你聊聊
Seth: Just let me talk to you.
去你媽的！
Fuck you. Fuck you!
- 請聽我解釋 - 他媽的..
- Just let me explain. - Eric: What the fuck?
- 他想佔我便宜 - 什麼？我沒有
- He tried to grab me. - Seth: What? No.
嘿 那不是真的 哥們
Hey, that is not true at all, man.
滾出去
Fuck off.
- 他傷到你嗎？- 我沒事
- Did he hurt you? - I'm fine.
你覺得這很好玩嗎
You think this is funny?
埃裏克 停下 停下來
Eric, stop. Stop it.
- 停下 - 算你走運 混蛋
- Stop it. - Laugh it up, dick head.
我來搞定
Let me handle this.
離她遠點
Get the fuck away from her.
別讓我在這裏再看到你
Don't you ever come back here.
也許該原路折返找找
Maybe if you retrace your steps.
不 它應該在這兒某個地方的
No. It's gotta be here somewhere.
上面有你的名字嗎？
Well, was your name in it?
或是聯繫方式之類的？
Or like any contact information?
你覺得呢？
What do you think?
翻譯：SystemNT-ch@subhd.com
臭婊子！
You fucking bitch!
克萊爾？你在嗎？
Claire? You here?
噓
Shh.
我給你注射的叫巴夫龍
What I just put in you is called pancuronium bromide.
一種麻醉劑 有點疼
It's a paralyzing agent. It stings a little.
不要擔心 無害的 我在自己身上試驗過
Don't worry, it's safe. I tested it on myself.
你來這裏幹什麼？
What you doing here?
哦 老闆娘半夜打電話
Oh, boss lady calls in the middle of the night,
叫我送貨進來
gotta make a delivery.
別急 哥們
Not so fast, man.
先簽個名
Sign in.
好的
Right.
- 不好意思 - 那是什麼？
- Excuse me. - The hell's that?
我想是滅虱粉
I think it's delousing powder.
好了 回頭見
All right, see you later.
- 你聽到了嗎？- 什麼？
- You hear that? - What?
- 有什麼不對勁嗎？- 噓
- Something wrong? - Shh.
- 你聽到什麼了嗎？- 安靜 哥們
- You hear something? - Quiet, man.
你也聽到了對嗎？
You heard that, right?
那個「呃」的聲音
That "uh" sound.
我啥也沒有聽到 是什麼？
I don't hear anything. What is it?
他媽的 是空調響
Fucking, ac, man.
總是出問題
Shit's always going out.
哦 可以了 可以了
Oh, I got it. I got it.
- 它壞了嗎？- 經常壞
- It's broken? - It's always broken.
- 這整個地方都很爛 - 好的
- This whole place sucks. - All right.
閉嘴
Shut up.
我是賽斯
So, I'm Seth.
怕你忘記了
In case you forgot.
去你媽的
Fuck you.
你自己選擇
Your choice.
- 去你媽的！- 我這樣做是為你好
- Fuck you! - I'm doing this for your own good.
我們明天再試試看
We'll try this again tomorrow.
去你媽的！
Fuck you!
嗨
Seth: Hi.
我給你帶了些水
I brought you some water.
給
Here.
喝
Drink this.
呼吸 呼吸 呼吸 坐起來
Breathe, breathe, breathe. Sit up.
抱歉
Sorry.
放輕鬆 沒事的
Take it easy. It's okay.
我也帶了些食物來
I brought food as well.
怕你餓了
In case you feel up for it.
水 食物
Water, food.
放輕鬆點 沒事的
Just take it easy, all right.
這些是你今天所有的食物
That's all you're getting today.
等等  請不要離開我
Wait! Please don't leave me.
我知道這很艱難
I know this is hard.
我也不好受
It's hard for me too.
但重要的是明確咱們之間的關係
But it's important to define our relationship.
設立一些界限
Establish some boundaries.
你這樣不管用的
This. This doesn't work.
這就對了
That's right.
我明天回來  到時我們再開始
I'll come back tomorrow. And we'll get started.
他會殺了你的
He's gonna kill you.
但你也知道
But you know that.
可能他會害怕起來
Maybe he'll lose his nerve, huh?
臨陣退縮
Chicken out.
或者某天他厭倦了
Or maybe he'll just get bored.
你說這些無濟於事
You're not helping.
他根本不需要槍  霍莉
He won't even need a gun, Holly.
他只需要離開這兒 你就死定了
All he has to do is walk away.
閉嘴
Shut up.
看看你
Claire: Look at you.
你要坐等他來抽你嗎？
You're letting him beat you?
等那個傻逼來抽你嗎？
That pathetic little shit?
如果你這麼容易屈服的話
If that's all it takes,
那麼也許你該被關在這裏
then maybe you deserve to be in there.
閉嘴！
Shut up!
你會強姦我嗎？
Are you gonna rape me?
不會
Seth: No.
殺了我？
Kill me?
我希望不會
I hope not.
你希望不會？
You hope not?
可能到時候我別無選擇
Might not have a choice.
為什麼？
And why's that?
我可能沒法救你
I might not be able to save you.
這是什麼意思 和宗教相關的原因嗎？
What is this, some kind of fucking religious thing?
是上帝讓你來懲罰所有的妓女之類的說辭嗎？
Did god tell you to punish all the whores, something like that?
這是一種不同類型的拯救
It's a different kind of saving.
- 不是宗教原因 - 所以呢 你只是個死變態而已
- And, no. - So what, you're just a sick fuck?
這是你取樂的方式？
This is how you get your kicks?
我這樣做不是為了我自己
I'm not doing this for me.
而是為了你
I'm doing this for you.
因為你很特別
Because you're special.
特別？
Special?
這是真的
It's true.
遇見你之前 我只是漂浮在人海中生活
Before I met you, i was just floating through life.
任何時候都可能迷失
Like any minute, i could just drift off.
沒有人會在意
No one would even notice.
然後你出現了
Then you came along.
關鍵是...
And the thing--
讓事情變得如此艱難的關鍵是..
the thing that made it so hard is,
我覺得你與眾不同
is I thought you were different.
你聰明 風趣
You're smart. Funny.
當你跟我說話時 你在看著我
When you talked to me, you saw me,
你真的看著我
you really saw me.
那只是你想讓我看到的一面 對嗎？
That's just what you wanted me to see, huh?
大家看得到的那個版本的霍莉
The version of Holly you are when everyone's watching.
但我們都知道那不是真的 不是嗎？
But we both know that's a lie, don't we?
去死吧
Go to hell.
這是問題所在
That's the question.
哪一個才是真正的霍莉？
Which one's the real Holly?
表面的霍莉還是另一個霍莉
The Holly on the outside or the other Holly.
因為如果有機會我可以救你
Because if there's even a chance I can save you,
我必須抓住它
I have to take it.
但如果你繼續頑固下去  沒什麼值得救的
But if that's it, if there's nothing left to save,
那麼你永遠不可能離開這個房間
then you're never leaving this room.
你在這裏幹什麼？
Nate: What you doing here?
哥們 如果讓他們抓到你在裏面搞事怎麼辦
Man, if they catch you fucking around them tunnels.
他們抓不到我  我不會進去的
They won't catch me, I'm not going in there.
去拿個拖把
Just grab a mop.
外面臭的跟狗屎一樣
We got that place smellin' like dog shit out there.
媽的
Shit.
那個傻子真可笑
This fuckin' dude is a joke.
那麼...
Claire: So...
你現在打算怎麼辦？
What are you gonna do now?
等..
I'm gonna wait.
好女孩
Claire: Good girl.
這真是一本讓人癡迷的書
Seth: It's a real page-Turner.
你真是一個作家 你知道嗎？
You're a hell of a writer, you know that?
你是個小偷
You're a thief.
現在要怎麼樣？
And now what?
突然間 你就琢磨透我了
Suddenly, you got me all figured out.
我希望如此  但沒有
I wish. No.
我主要是為你感到可憐
Mostly I just felt sorry for you.
你？你可憐我？
You? Felt sorry for me?
是啊 就是你談論愛情的那一部分
Yeah, it's the part where you talk about love.
「愛只是我們生理必然性的
"Love is just a label
一個標籤而已」
for our biological imperatives."
我不明白  我覺得這很愚蠢
I don't know. Felt ignorant to me.
你真的要給我講解愛情嗎 賽斯？
Are you really gonna lecture me on love, Seth?
你現在正把一個女孩關在籠子裏
You're keeping a girl in a cage.
我想我終於想清楚了
I think I finally figured it out.
所有那些把愛情比作
All these people who talk about love
天空閃電的人
like it's this lightning bolt from the sky.
這種不可抗力的
This irresistible force.
我可從來沒有那麼認為
So you think, well, I've never felt that.
那些人是錯誤的
But those people are wrong.
愛不是一道閃電
Love is not a lightning bolt.
愛是...真愛
Love is, real love,
需要努力付出
takes work.
需要犧牲
Sacrifice.
真愛就是為對方付出你的所有
Real love is giving everything you have to someone else.
- 那才是愛 - 他媽的開玩笑嗎？
- That's love. - Fucking kidding me?
你不這樣認為嗎？
You don't think?
「愛是犧牲」？
"Love is sacrifice"?
你知道誰相信這話嗎？那些討厭自己的人
You know who believes that? People who hate themselves.
那些和你一樣孤獨壓抑的人
Who are alone, depressed. Just like you.
- 你認為我討厭我自己？ - 我知道你是這樣的
- You think I have myself? - I know you do.
你如此厭惡自己  你甚至不敢想像
You hate yourself so much, you can't even imagine
什麼樣的鳥人才會接受你的愛
how fucked up someone would have to be to love you back.
所以你說服自己愛是一個可以買到的東西
So you convince yourself that love is this thing that you can buy.
你要做的就是不斷地給予
That all you have to do is keep giving.
就像我說的  我是在為你感到可憐
Well, like I said, i just feel sorry for you.
別他媽把可憐用到我身上
Spare me the fucking pity,
我不是這裏孤獨的那一個人
I'm not the one who's alone here.
噢  我想也不是
Oh, I guess not.
克萊爾這些天怎麼樣？
And how is Claire these days?
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
有時我打開那扇門之前
You know, sometimes before I open that door,
我聽到你在這裏面說話
I can heard you talking in here
和克萊爾說話
to Claire.
你能發出兩種聲音
The way you do two voices
一開始的時候把我給嚇壞了
scared the hell out of me at first.
你在胡說八道
You don't know what you're talking about.
我知道的比你想像的更多
I know more than you think.
她在這裏嗎 現在？
Is she here, right now?
沒有
No.
她不是真的
She's not real.
你覺得我不知道嗎？
You don't think i know that?
我想你已經開始忘記了
I think you're starting to forget
別疑神疑鬼的 埃裏克
don't get paranoid on me, Eric.
疑神疑鬼的時候就沒意思了
You're no fun when you're paranoid.
你病了  霍莉
Seth: You're sick, Holly.
你通過不斷地吃來麻痹
Feeding that sickness until all it does is eat.
你都琢磨透了 對嗎？
You just have it all figured out, don't you?
幾乎
Almost.
有一件事我還不明白
One thing i still don't understand.
日記
The journal.
首先 我瞭解到你和埃裏克要訂婚了
First, I get it. You and Eric getting engaged.
吧啦 吧啦...
Blah, blah, blah.
但你最好的朋友出現了 克萊爾 真克萊爾
But here comes your best friend, Claire. The real Claire.
霍莉吃不下 霍莉睡不著
Holly can't eat. Holly can't sleep.
霍莉想要面對他們  但她太害怕了
Holly wants to confront them but Holly's too scared.
去你媽的
Fuck you.
然後到這裏 事情開始變得十分有趣
Then here. Here's where it gets really interesting.
（克萊爾）：我回到家後...
Claire: I get home and there's like
看到德懷恩發來的大概20個訊息
20 messages from Dwayne, right?
比如「你在哪裏？」
He's like, "where are you?
為什麼還沒來接我？「
Why haven't you picked me up yet?"
其實是他自己說過
Even though, he's the one who said
星期六會來接我的
that he was coming to get me on Saturday.
你知道 莫名其妙地
You know, somehow of course
它就變成了是我的錯
it's just magically my fault.
你會告訴我嗎？
Were you going to tell me?
告訴你什麼？
Tell you what?
別這樣 克萊爾 你懂的
Come on, Claire. You know.
嗯 不太懂
Um, not really.
埃裏克
Eric.
你怎麼發現的？
How'd you find out?
他的郵箱 他不知道我有密碼
His email. He doesn't know i have the password.
- 糟糕 - 是的
- Shit - yeah.
霍莉 你讓我怎麼說？
Holly, what do you want me to say?
對不起
You know, I'm sorry.
我們喝的太醉了 可這並不意味著什麼
We were so drunk. And it didn't mean anything.
哦  既然這並不意味著什麼的話
Oh, well, as long as it didn't mean anything.
好了 霍莉 請減速
Okay, Holly, please slow the car down.
你讓我難以置信
You're unbelievable.
- 你知道嗎？- 對不起
- Do you know that? - I'm sorry.
你不知道我對那件事有多後悔
You have no idea how shitty I feel about this whole thing.
如果...該死的  請慢下來好嗎？
And if it-- damn it, please slow the car down, okay?
你本是我最好的朋友
You're supposed to be my best fucking friend.
霍莉 別這樣 天啊
Holly, come on. Jesus.
霍莉！該死的 你這樣會害死我們的
Holly! God damn it, you're gonna kill us.
哦 天哪  哦 我的天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my fucking god.
我們沒事的 我沒事
We're okay. I'm all right.
我們會沒事的 霍莉
We're gonna be okay, Holly.
We're okay, Holly.
我們會沒事的
We're gonna be fine.
We're gonna be okay.
我會沒事的
I'm gonna be fine.
你當那是什麼？
And you think that's what?
口供嗎？我是一個作家 賽斯
A confession? I'm a writer, Seth.
虛構是我的工作
Fiction's kind of what I do.
這就是為什麼我沒有直接報警的原因
Seth: That's why I didn't go straight to the police.
我必須確定一下
I had to be sure.
我跟蹤了你幾天
I thought I'd follow you around for a few days,
但你可沒有讓我久等
but you didn't make me wait long.
這麼做是有風險的
Seth: It was a risky move.
- （流浪漢）：不！- 即使你自己也是有危險的
- Homeless man: No! - Seth: Even for you.
這樣的事兒太多了
Seth: There were so many.
知道我怎麼想的嗎？
You want to know what I think?
我想你是希望自己被抓住
I think you wanted to get caught.
這就是為什麼你寫日記的原因
That's why you kept the journal.
您想要受到懲罰
You wanted to get punished.
所以我幸運地碰到了你
Lucky you came along .
你還不明白對嗎？
You don't get it, do you?
這不是懲罰
This isn't punishment.
我在試著拯救你
I'm trying to save you.
那就開始吧
Then do it.
拯救我
Save me.
我會的
I will.
我說到做到了
I meant what I said.
我會阻止你再去傷害他人
I'm gonna stop you hurting other people.
不管用什麼方法
One way or the other.
獲得奧斯卡獎的是...
And the Oscar goes to...
他想拯救我
He wants to save me.
我必須讓他相信有這樣的機會
I have to let him think there's a chance.
所以一切都是表演給他看嗎？
So that was all an act?
你剛只是在順水推舟？
You were just humoring him?
- 忽悠他... - 有話直說...
- Playing along... - If you've got something to say...
我只是想確定你是否還在繼續這場遊戲
I'm just making sure your head's still in the game.
我不需要多一次這樣無用的鼓勵 克萊爾
I don't need another useless pep talk, Claire.
我也不需要你
And I don't need you.
怎麼了？
Yes?
什麼？沒 沒什麼
What? No. Nothing.
只是好奇
Just was curious.
你為什麼要這樣做
Why you did it.
我想 當我看到埃裏克的電子郵件裏
I guess, when I saw Eric's email,
克萊爾發的那些消息
all those messages from Claire--
不 不是克萊爾的問題 我明白
no, not Claire. I understand that.
那是一種衝動型犯罪
It's a crime of passion or whatever.
我想知道為什麼你沒有就此停手
I wanna know why you didn't stop there.
為什麼要殺其他人
Why you killed the others.
因為你對克萊爾感到內疚
'Cause you feel guilty for what you did to Claire,
為了擺脫這種感覺而去做那些事兒
for getting away with it.
你想被抓住 不是嗎？
You wanted to get caught, didn't you?
不  因為我可以擺脫
No, because I could.
我不信
Yeah, I don't believe that.
我不在乎你信不信
Well, I don't care what you believe.
因為 聽著 事實是這樣的 賽斯
'Cause see, here's the thing, Seth.
當有人死在你面前 像克萊爾死的那樣
When someone dies in front of you, the way Claire died,
感覺世界瞬間清晰了
it's like you're whole world just snaps into focus.
求救嗎？
Cry for help?
這是一種打發時間的方式
It was a way to pass the time.
別裝作你很瞭解我
Don't pretend you know what I am.
你錯了 我的確瞭解你
You're wrong, i do know you.
我通過它瞭解你
I know you from this.
那個寫這些的女孩  她有夢想
And the girl who wrote this, you had dreams.
她關心其他人
She cared about people.
她害怕孤獨
Who's scared to be alone.
這才是真正的你
This is the real you.
不是..
Not...
賽斯有點愛上我了
Seth's got a little crush.
這不是關於我們的事兒
This isn't about us.
如果你愛某種東西 就給它自由
If you love something, set it free.
事情不就是這樣的嗎？
Isn't that how that goes?
你知道 我不能這樣做
You know I can't do that.
你知道把一頭大白鯊
Do you know what happens to a great white shark
扔到水族館裏會怎麼樣嗎？
when you put him inside an aquarium?
它會用自己的腦袋猛擊玻璃
It bashes its brains against the glass.
每次都會
Every time.
來吧
Come on.
停下 霍莉 停下！
Stop, Holly, stop!
停下 霍莉！
Stop, Holly!
你明天下來的時候會怎麼做
What are you gonna do when you come down here tomorrow
看到我直挺挺地死在這兒的時候
and I'm belly up in the tank, huh?
因為你沒法棄之不顧
'Cause you can't just walk away.
這裏到處都是你的指紋
Not with your finger prints all over the place.
我自殺了 你也會沒命
I kill myself, your life ends too.
所以把這作為咱們關係的界限如何
So how's that for the boundaries of our fucking relationship?
- 賽斯？- 嗯？
- Seth? - Hmm?
工作做完後到我辦公室來
Finish this up and come see me in my office.
有什麼問題嗎？
Something wrong?
「有什麼問題嗎？」這正是我要問你的
"Is something wrong?" That's the question, isn't it?
我不太明白你說的
I'm not following you.
那些狗捨現在都髒兮兮的
The kennels are filthy.
我們儲藏室裏現在都有臭蟲了
We've got bugs up in the stock room.
但賽斯去哪兒了？他肯定沒來上過班
And where's Seth? He's not here, that's for sure.
內特說你兩天都沒來上班了
Nate says you haven't been here in two days.
甘迪夫人 內特幾乎不..
Mrs. gundy, Nate is hardly--
內特的工作做的很好
Nate does his job.
你也該做好你自己的工作
You should've done yours.
你要解雇我嗎？
You're firing me?
這次給你警示
Disciplinary notice.
並且記錄在永久檔案中
This goes in your permanent record.
再犯一次 立馬走人 明白嗎？
One more strike and you're gone. Understand?
明白  謝謝
Understood. Thank you.
你不知道這工作對我有多重要
You don't know how much this means to me.
這是將要發生在你身上的事情
This, this is what's gonna happen to you
當你認為自己在掌控之中
when you think you're in control.
你認為你在掌控之中 霍莉
You think you're in control, Holly.
好 這是將要發生的事情 當你認為你在..
Well, this is what'll happen when you think you're in--
我掌控著情況
-  I control the situation.
我來做一些維護工作
There's the man. Just doing some maintenance.
沒要求你來
Didn't ask.
嘿  賽斯 我這有你的工資單
Hey, Seth. I got your paycheck.
還健在 嗯？
Still here, huh?
其餘在哪裏？
Where's the rest?
沒有其餘的
There is no rest.
當你開始掌控自己的時候 事情就變這樣了
This is what happens when you start acting like you're in control.
這可不夠
That's not enough.
這不是由你決定的
You don't get to decide that.
去你的
Fuck you.
去我的？我為你操碎了心
Fuck me? I go through hell for you
而你在幹什麼  威脅我？
and what do you do, threaten me?
你再說這種話
You ever pull that shit again,
我要讓你體會一下真正的絕食是什麼感覺
I'll show you what a real hunger strike feels like.
去你的
Fuck you.
我昨晚做了個夢  夢中有你
I had a dream last night and you were in it.
只有咱們倆
It was just the two of us.
我們在水下的一個房子裏
And we were in this house down by the water.
我想 我們已經生活在那很長時間了
And I think we'd been living there a long time
因為那裏牆上掛著一些照片
'cause there were these pictures on the walls.
我們倆的照片
Pictures of us.
看著很奇怪
It was weird looking at them,
因為看著感覺挺好
because something about it felt right.
就像這裏 這整個世界就是一個夢
Like this, this whole world is a dream
而海灘上的那座房子是真的
and that house on the beach, that's reality.
事情原本應該是這樣的
That's how things are supposed to be.
也許我可以到自動售貨機
Seth: Maybe I can get you some snacks
給你買些點心
from the vending machine.
謝謝你 賽斯
Thanks, Seth.
我的老天啊
Holy shit.
牆上有個燈
There's a light on the wall.
嘿 你叫什麼名字？
Hey, what's your name?
嗯 我叫內特
Um, I'm Nate.
聽我說 內特
Listen to me, Nate.
你得找工具斷這鎖
You have to find something to break open this lock.
你能做到嗎？
Can you do that?
這亂糟糟的是怎麼...
What kind of fucked up...
- 是賽斯干的嗎？- 內特 現在沒時間想這些
- Did Seth do this? - Nate, there's no time for that right now.
好的 選好角度猛擊它
Okay, go at it hard, at an angle.
我們得打電話叫人  警察或什麼的
We gotta call somebody, the cops or whatever.
你得馬上把我放出去
You have to get me out of here right now.
繼續 試試
Holly: Keep going, try now.
我就是在這麼干
Nate: That's what I'm doing.
再使點勁
Harder.
這亂七八糟的
Nate: This is all fucked up.
好的 很棒
Okay, that's great.
我數三下
Nate: Okay, on three. All right?
一 二 三
One, two, three.
等等
Hold on.
你知道什麼是真愛嗎 內特？
Do you know what real love is, Nate?
- 什麼？- 真愛
- What? - Holly: You know, real love.
如果你愛過某人  但她生病了
Say you loved somebody. But she got sick.
然後某一天來了個人
And then someone came along one day
把她身上的管子拔掉
to pull the plug on her
從你身邊永遠帶走了她
to take her away from you forever.
你會怎麼做？
What would you do?
我不知道 我只是想把你放出來
Nate: I don't know, I just wanna get you outta here.
你會採取一切辦法
Holly: You would do anything
阻止它發生
to stop that from happening.
任何方法 不計代價
Anything at all, no matter what the cost
因為那就是愛的本質
because that's what love is.
愛是犧牲
Love is sacrifice.
臥槽你？
What the fuck?
你完蛋了
You die.
噢
Oh.
你在刺我嗎？
Are you stabbing me?
混蛋
Motherfucker!
那塊磚 賽斯 用那塊水泥磚
The block, Seth. Use the cinder block.
他還在動 快呀 搬起來
He's moving. Come on, use it.
- 我不能 - 你必須
- I can't. - You have to.
賽斯  我不能失去你
Seth, I can't lose you.
- 求求你？- 噢 操
- Please? - Nate: Oh, fuck.
我的腿沒知覺了
I can feel my leg.
他媽的
What the fuck?
救命啊
Somebody help me.
來 再來一遍
come on, do it again.
再來一次
One more time.
對不起 對不起 對不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
賽斯 你得聽我的 懂嗎？
Seth. You have to listen to me, okay?
你必須完全按我說的做
You have to do exactly what I say.
你在聽嗎？
Are you listening?
第一步：處理掉屍體
Okay, step one is disposing of the body.
越快越好
The sooner, the better.
燒了 埋了 沉水裏 怎麼都行
Okay, burn it, bury it, sink it, whatever.
只要把它弄出這裏就行
Just get it out of here.
但是在銷毀可能的線索前
But you can't do that
你不能這麼做
before you get rid of the identifiers.
牙齒 紋身 指紋
Teeth, tattoos, fingerprints.
指紋簡單 用角豆處理就行
The fingerprints are easy, you can use a carob for that.
牙齒要分散開來
After the teeth, you need to scatter them.
扔垃圾袋 或扔水中 怎樣都行
Dumpsters, in water, whatever.
只要不把全部扔在同一個地方就行
Just not all in the same place.
所以要考慮的只剩軀體了
And then there's just the body to worry about.
他這樣塞不進焚化爐
Seth: He's not gonna fit in the incinerator.
嗯  不可能
Holly: Well, not like that.
你要和我練習一下怎麼說嗎？
Holly: Do you want to practice with me what to say?
嗨 甘迪夫人 我是賽斯
Seth: Hey, Mrs. gundy, it's Seth.
抱歉這麼晚了給你打電話
Sorry to call you so late.
嗯 是的 內特叫我在前台看著
Um, yeah, Nate asked me to watch the front
他出去辦點事 到現在還沒有回來
while he ran some errands and he's still not back yet.
我不知道他去哪兒了
I don't know where he went.
好的  晚安
Oh... Okay, good night.
抱歉
Sorry.
你感覺怎麼樣？
How do you feel?
我不知道 感覺有點分裂
I don't know. Disconnected.
就像是發生在別人身上似的 你明白嗎？
Like it happened to someone else, you know?
第一次總是最糟糕的
The first time's always the worst.
不是什麼第一次 剛只是一個意外
There is no first time. It was an accident.
- 我告訴過你的 - 你知道是什麼促使我不斷這麼做嗎？
- I told you. - You know what always got to me?
問題就在這兒
It was the questions.
我記得一開始的時候
I remember in the beginning
我所想的都是如果她有個寵物怎麼辦？
all I could think about was what if she had a pet?
一隻可憐的小狗坐在門口
It's poor little doggie just sitting by the door
正等著她回家
waiting for her to come home.
但所有這一切都消失了
But all that goes away.
你想的越多
The more you think about it
越是會記起你喜歡的那些
the more you remember the parts that you liked.
當你掌控著自己的生活
How it made you feel.
那是一種什麼樣的感覺
Like you were in control of your life
第一次你感到什麼也傷害不了你
for the very first time, like nothing could hurt you.
不是那樣的
That's not how it was.
但唯一的問題是
But the only problem is
或早或晚 這一切又都恢復正常
that sooner or later it all goes back to normal.
突然間 你沒什麼特別的了 你只是你
All of a sudden you're nothing special, you're just you.
停下好嗎？
Stop, okay?
然後你就開始思考
Holly: And that's when you start to wonder.
要走多遠才能找回那種感覺
How far you'd have to go to get that feeling back.
這是不一樣的
It's not the same.
接受自己真面目沒什麼可恥的 賽斯
There is no shame in accepting what you are, Seth.
我這麼做是為了我們的安全
I did it, to keep us safe.
我別無選擇
I had no choice.
你沒有想過為什麼...
Didn't you ever wonder why
世界上有這麼多女孩而你只喜歡我？
all the girls in the world but you get a hard on for me?
你會認為這是一個巧合嗎？
And you think that's, what, a coincidence?
你和我  咱們生來就是做這個的
You and me, we were born to do this.
別裝作你很瞭解我似的
Don't act like you know a goddamn thing about me.
我知道一個正常人發現他人的殺人自白書後
I know that a normal person finds a murder confession
會去報警
and goes to the police.
而不是到寵物市場來
Not to petsmart.
哦 是的 我應該報警說「打擾一下 長官
Oh, yeah, "excuse me, officer.
你看到那女孩了嗎？那個女服務員？她就是少年漢尼拔
You see that girl over there, the waitress? She's Hannibal Lecter.
我怎麼知道的？我闖進她家裏偷她東西發現的」
You know how I know? I broke into her apartment and stole her shit."
這能行嗎？
Think that'll work?
噢 那麼也可以說是綁架？
Oh, and so plan b is kidnapping?
「也可以說
'Cause the fucking alternative
我四處跟蹤你 坐著看你傷人」
was sitting around watching you hurt someone else.
嗯
Mm.
是啊  你沒有傷害過人
Good thing no one got hurt.
我告訴過你...我告訴過你
I told you... I told you.
這是一個意外
It's an accident.
面對它吧  賽斯
Face it, Seth.
這從來就不是拯救生命之類的事情 你會喜歡的
This was never about saving lives, you like this.
你想要具備那種力量
You like having that kind of power.
決定誰生誰死
Deciding who lives, who dies.
霍莉 還不算太晚
Holly, it's not too late.
我可以拯救你的 拜託
I can save you, please.
拜託 我可以拯救你
Please. I can save you.
也許你不該拯救我
Maybe you're not supposed to save me.
也許是我該拯救你
Maybe I'm suppose to save you.
別 別
Don't, don't.
賽斯 請幫幫我 我很冷
Seth, please help me, I'm so cold.
來溫暖我
Please make me warm.
你可以幫我嗎 你能讓我溫暖嗎？
Can you help me, can you please make me warm?
我以為你愛我
I thought you love me.
我確實愛你
I do.
我真的愛你
I do love you.
霍莉 霍莉
Holly. Holly.
霍莉
Holly.
我會盡快回來的
I'll come back as soon as I can.
- 賽斯 - 哦
- Oh. - Seth.
這是偵探米拉
This is detective Mira.
有什麼事嗎？
Something wrong?
咱們找個地方聊聊吧？
Detective: Is there somewhere we can talk?
你和內特是同事對吧？
So, you work with Nathan, yeah?
是
Yes.
你最後一次見到他是什麼時候？
When's the last time you saw him?
週三 我想是 週三晚上
Wednesday, I think? Wednesday evening.
是的 他讓我來前台守著
Yeah, he asked me to cover the front
他要出去辦點事
while he ran some errands.
- 什麼樣的事？- 嗯 他沒有說
- What kind of errands? - Um, he didn't say.
嗯 那是大概...
Uh-huh. And this would be about...
幾點？
What time?
九點 十點 差不多那段時間
9:00, 10:00. Something like that.
他是從前面離開的嗎？
He leave out through the front?
是
Yeah.
前門 你確定嗎？
The front door, you sure?
是的 怎麼了？
Yeah, why?
事情是這樣
Well, here's the thing.
前門是無鑰匙進出系統
The front door operates on a keyless entry system.
你也知道 每次進出都會有記錄
As you know, it records each instance in or out.
現在你猜最後一次有人開那門是什麼時候？
Now you wanna guess the last time someone opened that door?
四點 凌晨四點
4:00. That's 4:00 am.
- 嗯 - 而你說是下午九點或十點？
- Huh. - And you said it was what, 9:00 or 10:00pm?
這有點奇怪 你不覺得嗎？
It's kind of weird, don't you think?
不 也許是我記錯了
No, maybe I'm remembering it wrong.
他可能是從側門走的 或倉庫走的
He could have left out the side door, or loading docks.
倉庫？哦 當然 是啊
Loading docks? Oh, sure. Yeah.
我應該去查一下的
I should check that out.
你和內特是朋友？
You and Nathan friends?
我們一起工作 他人挺好
Well, we worked together. He was a nice guy and all.
但他卻想讓上司解雇你..
Until he tried to get you fired.
什麼？事情不是這樣的
What? Oh. That is not what happened.
內特和我以前是朋友
Nate and i were friends.
哦 現在你們又是朋友了
Oh, now you're friends again.
或者你們以前是朋友 過去式
Or you were friends, past tense.
這是你第二次這麼說
That's the second time you said that.
你知道有句俗話說
Well, you know what they say.
第一次是糊弄  第二次是招供
First time 's confusion, second time's confession.
這是幹什麼？
What's this about?
標準程序而已
Standard procedure.
所以他叫你替他看著
So now, he asked you to cover for him,
是星期三晚上 九點還是十點？
this is what Wednesday night, nine or ten?
他說過他要去哪裏嗎？
Did he say where he was going?
我想他是要去見某人
I think he had to meet someone.
他接了個電話
He got a phone call, something.
這很有趣 因為我們做的第一件事
It's funny, because the first thing we did
就是檢查電話記錄
was check the phone records.
最後一次和他通話的是他女友
And the last person he talked to was his girlfriend.
那天下午5:32
5:32 that afternoon.
嗨
Hi.
你得吃點東西
Gotta eat something.
霍利 別這樣
Holly, come on.
快 快 不要這樣
Come on. Come on, don't do this.
現在我知道你在做什麼
Seth: Now I know what you're doing.
這沒用的
It's not gonna work.
求你和我說說話
Just talk to me, please.
結束了  賽斯
Holly: It's over, Seth.
我不明白
I don't understand.
因為如果你不能幫助我
Because if you can't help me
不能給我我需要的 那麼就沒人可以了
if you can't give me what I need, then no one can.
告訴我  告訴我你需要什麼
Tell me, tell me what you need.
你知道答案的
You know the answer.
你把我放在一個籠子裏
You put me in a box.
這不是愛 這是佔有
That's not love, that's ownership.
你什麼也沒給
You didn't give me anything.
你所做的都是取
All you did was take.
我不能讓你出去
I can't let you out.
- 你知道的 - 我沒有要求你放我出去
- You know that. - I didn't ask you to.
那麼你想要什麼？
Then what? What do you want?
一個證明
Proof.
證明？
Proof?
- 一根手指 - 什麼？
- A finger. - A what?
一根手指？
A finger?
我的手指？
My finger?
不
No.
不不不...
No. No. No. No.
這太扯了
This is fucked.
你不明白嗎？
Can't you see that?
這完全是在亂來
This is totally fucked.
不行  我正在努力拯救你
No. I'm trying to save you here.
我正在給你機會
And I'm trying to let you.
你不能要求我那麼做  霍莉
Well, you can't ask me for that, Holly.
我不會做的
And I'm not gonna do it.
我以前認為我是唯一的那個
I used to think i was the only one.
即使我是一個孩子時 我也知道
Even when I was a kid, i still knew.
如果他們發現了
That if they ever found out,
我的家人  我的朋友們...
my family, my friends...
如果他們知道我的真面目  他們會轉身就跑的
If they knew what I really was, they'd run the other way.
所以我學會了...
And so you learn to...
調和 偽裝
Blend in, to fake it.
過不久..
After a while,
甚至不會注意到自己有多孤獨
you don't even notice how lonely you really are.
但是之後...
But then...
有人出現了
Someone comes along,
像你這樣的人
someone like you.
即使他什麼都還不知道
Even if he just doesn't know it yet.
突然間
And all of a sudden,
你開始想..
you start thinking,
也許未必非要採取這種方式
maybe it doesn't have to be this way.
也許我未必非得孤獨
Maybe I don't have to be alone.
所以放開了手中的繩子
And so let go of the rope.
因為這個人  他不會讓你跌倒
Because this person, he's not gonna let you fall.
他會抓住你 你知道會的
He's gonna catch you. You know it.
至少這就是你一直對自己說的
At least that's what you keep telling yourself.
自始至終都是
The whole way down.
不要再回來
Don't come back.
如果我在你心中無足輕重
If that's all i am to you,
如果我只是一隻寵物
if I'm just a pet.
那麼不要再回來看我了
Then don't come back for me.
不要再回來看我
Don't come back for me.
如果我為你這麼做
If I do this for you,
你就會相信我了嗎？
then you'll believe?
是的
Yes.
這是不對的
This is wrong.
賽斯  你愛我
Seth, you love me.
沒有比這兒更正確的
There is nothing more right than that.
你就要成功了
You're almost there.
打開門
Open the door.
- 你在做什麼？- 快打開門
- What are you doing? - Open the fucking door.
你已經斷了一根指頭 賽斯
You're already down a finger, Seth.
你還準備再失去多少？
How much more are you ready to lose?
退後
Get back.
霍莉
Holly.
等等 你在做什麼？
Wait. What are you doing?
噓
Shh.
我相信你
I believe you.
是嗎？
You do?
你...
Do you...
你救了我  賽斯
You saved me, Seth.
當然我愛你
Of course i love you.
但你知道那意味著什麼
But you know what that means.
霍莉
Holly.
不要離開我
Don't leave me.
哦 天啊
Oh, god.
你為這些東西忙了多年
Eric: You've been working on these pieces for years.
我知道 我沒說我不興奮
Holly: I know, I'm not saying I'm not excited.
能接到那個電話會開心死的
It's like great to get that call.
- 我只是 - 我以為你會更興奮的
- I just-- - I figured you'd be more psyched about this.
要出版了是件大事
It's a big deal, getting published.
這是一次自費出版 不是像《紐約客》那樣的
It's just a vanity press, it's not exactly "the new yorker."
除了這點  仍然感覺很棒
Screw that, it's still awesome.
我為你感到驕傲
I'm proud of you.
我以為你不會喜歡我的小說
I thought you didn't even like my story.
我喜歡你
I like you.
- 嘿 寶貝 能把電話遞給我嗎？- 好的
- Hey, babe, can you grab my phone? - Yeah.
嘿 種馬 整天都在想你 記得打電話給我 xoxo
給
Here you go.
謝謝 寶貝
Thank you, babe.
嗨
Hi.
我今天和埃裏克又鬧得不太愉快
I had another bad day with Eric.
他仍在和其它女孩亂搞
He's still fooling around with other girls.
今天早上 我幾乎要傷他
This morning I almost hurt him.
但我想起了你
But then I thought of you.
想起你有多愛我
And how much you love me.
和你在為我做的事
And what you're doing for me.
然後我感覺好多了
Then I felt better.
《寵物》